!trigger_p_1:Go down the stairs and find the entrance to the training room.
Use the following keys to move:
Forward: W, Backward: S, Left: A, Right: D.
Use the mouse to control camera position and orientation. The movement direction is affected by the camera.#
!trigger_p_2:Go in between the containers.#
!trigger_p_3:Enter the shooting range and take the weapon from the table.
Press left mouse button to shoot. Press Q to change a weapon and R to reload a weapon.#
!trigger_p_4:Get onto the ring and practice hand-to-hand combat.
Press either left or right mouse button to attack.#
!trigger_p_5:You can climb this wall.
Move close the the wall and press E to enter the climbing mode.
Use the mouse to move hands and legs. If the circle is green
the spot is safe enough to secure and pull up. Move your hands
and legs to reach the top of the wall.#
!trigger_p_6:You can climb this wall.
Move close the the wall and press E to enter the climbing mode.
Use the mouse to move hands and legs. If the circle is green
the spot is safe enough to secure and pull up. Move your hands
and legs to reach the top of the wall.#